[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "I mean it all sounds very odd doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "all", "sounds", "very", "odd", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, honestly when you look at these two men, former President Clinton was a very effusive, excessive guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "honestly", "when", "you", "look", "at", "these", "two", "men", ",", "former", "President", "Clinton", "was", "a", "very", "effusive", ",", "excessive", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Finally and break to me if you don't mind Candy, I mean is he going to be rather icy when the Vice President arrives for his morning coffee at the White House tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", "and", "break", "to", "me", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "Candy", ",", "I", "mean", "is", "he", "going", "to", "be", "rather", "icy", "when", "the", "Vice", "President", "arrives", "for", "his", "morning", "coffee", "at", "the", "White", "House", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well I would think probably the happiest person tonight is Hillary Clinton, not to be sitting in the White House as Vice President because in they're in so many trouble right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "would", "think", "probably", "the", "happiest", "person", "tonight", "is", "Hillary", "Clinton", ",", "not", "to", "be", "sitting", "in", "the", "White", "House", "as", "Vice", "President", "because", "in", "they", "'re", "in", "so", "many", "trouble", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Great this is so much fun, I know nothing about this book so you'll get my immediate, spontaneous reaction.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "this", "is", "so", "much", "fun", ",", "I", "know", "nothing", "about", "this", "book", "so", "you", "'ll", "get", "my", "immediate", ",", "spontaneous", "reaction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Now it's over, Democrats on the right, the President, this book has a more ripping each others throats are, you must be distraught?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "it", "'s", "over", ",", "Democrats", "on", "the", "right", ",", "the", "President", ",", "this", "book", "has", "a", "more", "ripping", "each", "others", "throats", "are", ",", "you", "must", "be", "distraught", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "It looks like Christmas everyday.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "looks", "like", "Christmas", "everyday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Would it made any difference to Mitt Romney if his running mate have been Chris Christie?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "made", "any", "difference", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "if", "his", "running", "mate", "have", "been", "Chris", "Christie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I don't think so because the reason Romney lost, well two reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "because", "the", "reason", "Romney", "lost", ",", "well", "two", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Yeah it's in my book.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "it", "'s", "in", "my", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "That does mean it's true?", "question_tokens": ["That", "does", "mean", "it", "'s", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "It's in their book.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "in", "their", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "But hypothetically if it does?", "question_tokens": ["But", "hypothetically", "if", "it", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "It can't.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kenya"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "VBG", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Send him back to Kenya, what does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["Send", "him", "back", "to", "Kenya", ",", "what", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "It means nothing, it's a reference to Kenya people laugh because the birth (ph) or thing is crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "means", "nothing", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "reference", "to", "Kenya", "people", "laugh", "because", "the", "birth", "(", "ph", ")", "or", "thing", "is", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kenya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Is it clearly a joke?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "clearly", "a", "joke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "It's clearly not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "clearly", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Why are the rules so different with the Democrats?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "the", "rules", "so", "different", "with", "the", "Democrats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I'm not talking about, I mean 50 years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "talking", "about", ",", "I", "mean", "50", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Is there a nasty sides of the tea party which seeps through with comments like that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "nasty", "sides", "of", "the", "tea", "party", "which", "seeps", "through", "with", "comments", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Does he represent a mindset?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "represent", "a", "mindset", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "It's a joke, this is the guy's father.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "joke", ",", "this", "is", "the", "guy", "'s", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "It's funny really?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "funny", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "It always kills because it's silly.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "always", "kills", "because", "it", "'s", "silly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Silly?", "question_tokens": ["Silly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No one...", "answer_tokens": ["No", "one", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What did he have to say about you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "have", "to", "say", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "That's trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Do you ?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "You're not on everything.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "on", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Is it technically possible for a guy like Ted Cruz to be the Republican nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "technically", "possible", "for", "a", "guy", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "to", "be", "the", "Republican", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Sure, I hope so, I mean it's very hard to make prediction this far out.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "I", "hope", "so", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "'s", "very", "hard", "to", "make", "prediction", "this", "far", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Can he do it with his current policies as he espouses them or will he inevitably have to move more to the center?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "do", "it", "with", "his", "current", "policies", "as", "he", "espouses", "them", "or", "will", "he", "inevitably", "have", "to", "move", "more", "to", "the", "center", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Not on the things he's been talking about, I mean ObamaCare is falling apart right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "on", "the", "things", "he", "'s", "been", "talking", "about", ",", "I", "mean", "ObamaCare", "is", "falling", "apart", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Was is it worth shutting down the government with all the pain that cost?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "is", "it", "worth", "shutting", "down", "the", "government", "with", "all", "the", "pain", "that", "cost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Well, we didn't shut it down.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "shut", "it", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Are you going out tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "out", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "I usually, it's my favorite holiday.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "usually", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "favorite", "holiday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Are you going to dress up and go down to Sunset Boulevard in some wacky custome?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "dress", "up", "and", "go", "down", "to", "Sunset", "Boulevard", "in", "some", "wacky", "custome", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I'm on a book tour, I'm going to home and going to bed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "on", "a", "book", "tour", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "home", "and", "going", "to", "bed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sunset Boulevard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Red Sox"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Let me ask you first, what was your reaction when you saw the Red Sox winning the World Series in this outpouring of love for Boston Strong?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "first", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "Red", "Sox", "winning", "the", "World", "Series", "in", "this", "outpouring", "of", "love", "for", "Boston", "Strong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "It's great, I mean the Red Sox were behind all us victims, the whole time.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "great", ",", "I", "mean", "the", "Red", "Sox", "were", "behind", "all", "us", "victims", ",", "the", "whole", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Red Sox"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What is your condition at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "condition", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Sort of really sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["Sort", "of", "really", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What does being -- or what does the phrase, \"Boston Strong,\" mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "being", "--", "or", "what", "does", "the", "phrase", ",", "``", "Boston", "Strong", ",", "''", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I mean, to me, it means -- the first responders, the people in our city, I don't take it as -- for us, the victims, I don't feel it fits us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "to", "me", ",", "it", "means", "--", "the", "first", "responders", ",", "the", "people", "in", "our", "city", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "take", "it", "as", "--", "for", "us", ",", "the", "victims", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "feel", "it", "fits", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What message would you like it to send, the New York Marathon, to the world if you like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "message", "would", "you", "like", "it", "to", "send", ",", "the", "New", "York", "Marathon", ",", "to", "the", "world", "if", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, I think the message is that, you know, any city can be strong.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "message", "is", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "any", "city", "can", "be", "strong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New York Marathon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Who told you to do that and how did you feel when you did it?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "told", "you", "to", "do", "that", "and", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "did", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "You know, I was against the idea, originally, because it just seem like kind of a weird psychedelic song from the '60s where the astronaut dies at the end.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "against", "the", "idea", ",", "originally", ",", "because", "it", "just", "seem", "like", "kind", "of", "a", "weird", "psychedelic", "song", "from", "the", "'60s", "where", "the", "astronaut", "dies", "at", "the", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Well, what does his e-mail say?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "does", "his", "e-mail", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Just -- yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "--", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["2001 Space Odyssey"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Does that over-ride any of the technical things?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "over-ride", "any", "of", "the", "technical", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, I mean I was really inspired by 2001 Space Odyssey.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "was", "really", "inspired", "by", "2001", "Space", "Odyssey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Pierce"]}, "docId": "131031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "I -- was it only it was cracked up to be when you dreamed of this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "--", "was", "it", "only", "it", "was", "cracked", "up", "to", "be", "when", "you", "dreamed", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "It was this little boy's dream too, Pierce.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "this", "little", "boy", "'s", "dream", "too", ",", "Pierce", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]